CURRICULUM VITAE

DIVYA BARMATE

Personal Details

Contact Details:

Phone: +91 6355294308

Email: Barmatedivya@gmail.com

Other Details:

Daughter of :MR. N.D BARMATE

Date of Birth: 28th Dec 1995

Sex : Female

Nationality: Indian

Marital Status: Single

Present Address:

K102, Orchid White field, besides Palm greens, Near torrent power station, Makarba, Ahmedabad. 380015

Permanent Address:

H pocket 5/a ,maroda sector, bhilai C.G 490006

Career Objective

I have started working since 2017. Since then I have been working under customer service profile. Till now I have gained good experience in handling customer operations and capable enough to understand any kind of work and process. I here by would like to convey that i am career oriented and always chase for knowledge and growth.

Educational Qualification

I have completed my 10th and 12th from CBSE board from BSP senior secondary school sector - 7, in Chhattisgarh.

Currently pursuing Bachelor in Arts, Political Science Honours (BAPSH) from Ignou University.

Additional Qualification

MS Office

Presentation Skills

Interpersonal Skills

Experience

Working as Client Service Executive in Aditadv Digital Pvt. Ltd since 22 June 2020.

Worked as Customer service agent in **Unipath solutions (UK process) in Ahmedabad** from 14 Dec 2018 to 31 March 2020.

Worked as Customer relations agent in **Vodafone shared service** UK Process in Ahmedabad from May 2017 to June 2018

Worked as Customer service agent in **IBM Daksh Concentrix** in Pune from July 2016 to March 2017

Worked as CSO in INDIGO AIRLINES in Pune from October 2015 to July 2016

Worked as a **Tr. customer service exc** in **Go Airlines in Pune** from June 2015 to October 2015

Strengths

Quick Learner.

Leadership Quality.

Creative

Initiator

Smart worker

Declaration

I hereby de	eclare that the	above give	n informatio	n in the resu	ame is true to	o the best o	f my
knowledge	and belief.						

Date:

Yours sincerely,

Divya Barmate

Place: Ahmedabad